<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<inm:Results productTitle="Inmagic DB/Text WebPublisher PRO" productVersion="11.00" xmlns:inm="http://www.inmagic.com/webpublisher/query" oex="ISO-8859-1">
<inm:Recordset AC="QBE_QUERY" sn="AUTO32607" se="10860" queryCount="91" page="1" pageCount="1" setCount="91">
<inm:Record setEntry="0">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Jon Faine</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>31 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>10:54 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:00</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Interview with Frances Bell, State political reporter. Faine says Bell is on her way to a meeting of Coalition MPs in Creswick. He refers to The Australian report today that Ted Baillieu has &apos;had the riot act read to him&apos;. Bell says the meeting started yesterday and was organised well in advance of the story. She notes it is an annual meeting about direction and vision of the Coalition. She suggests there has been a fair amount of &apos;disgruntlement&apos; behind the scenes about the government direction. She says the perception is that Baillieu is not selling the achievements of the government. She points out he has had a change of strategy, but it is not being reflected in polls. She refers to two Newspoll results, and a Channel Seven ReachTEL poll.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Frances Bell, State political reporter</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Public opinion polls - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Political Parties - Liberal Party - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Mornings 31_01_13 Bell.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="1">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Jon Faine</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>31 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>10:39 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:13</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Faine says there are problems in the Victorian Liberal Party, not just the SA Liberal Party. He says he hopes to look at it shortly. He says The Australian is reporting today that just before Christmas a number of Liberal Party powerbrokers said Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier, had to change his strategy and approach. He says Isobel Redmond, SA Opposition Leader, has just resigned after a couple of disappointing years in the position. He says there is speculation Alexander Downer, former Howard Government Foreign Affairs Minister, is positioning to enter as Opposition Leader.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee />
<inm:Subject>Public opinion polls - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Political Parties - Liberal Party - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Mornings 31_01_13 leadership.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="2">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>31 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>10:08 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:23</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Regular Segment: Jeff Kennett, Chairman, beyondblue. Mitchell says The Australian is reporting that Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier, has been told to lift his game or be dumped. Kennett says it is by John Ferguson, journalist. He says every leader including the PM, Opposition Leader, and &apos;Ted&apos;, is under scrutiny. He denies knowing if Baillieu was told this. He refers to his own history with polls and being elected.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Jeff Kennett, Chairman, beyondblue</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Public opinion polls - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 31_01_13 Kennett.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="3">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Jon Faine</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>31 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:36 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>5:32</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Interview with Meredith Peace, Victorian Branch Secretary, Australian Education Union. Faine says school is back and the teachers dispute is continuing. Peace discusses working with Mary Bluett. She says they have been calling for the Government to return to the negotiating table. She&apos;s hopeful the Premier will put forward a reasonable offer. Peace says they need to resolve the dispute. Faine mentions he invited Minister Martin Dixon to join him but the offer was declined. Peace says the Government has threatened court action. Faine notes The Australian reports there was a party room rebellion against Ted Baillieu. Peace says internal Liberal Party politics isn&apos;t relevant.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Meredith Peace, Victorian Branch Secretary, Australian Education Union</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Teachers</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Industrial disputes</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Mornings 31_01_13 Peace.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="4">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>31 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:26 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:38</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Regular Segment: Robert Doyle, Lord Mayor, Melbourne City Council. Caller Ed says his daughter went to a &apos;meet and greet&apos; by The Janoskians. He says they tweeted they were having a thing to get on the Ellen show at Federation Square. He notes it was not organised through Federation Square. He says police were there. He says there were &apos;crowd rushes&apos;, and his daughter came home in tears. Doyle discusses rules regarding Federation Square, noting it is controlled under a separate body with the State Victorian Government. He refers to concerns about public liability insurance.
Mitchell says he just received a message from former Labor Minister for Roads Tim Pallas, who was minister at the time of the crash in the Burnley Tunnel. He says the VicRoads reasoning against banning lane changing is the design prohibits it. He refers to an access lane at Power St. He reads the message, regarding exiting at Burnley St. Doyle agrees slowing down is worth consideration.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Robert Doyle, Lord Mayor, Melbourne City Council</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Melbourne - City Squares</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 31_01_13 caller Ed.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="5">
<inm:StationProg>ABC TV News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Ian Henderson</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>19:18 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:13</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Classes resumed for many students today. In the background, teachers and the Victorian Government continued to squabble over pay. Preps at Debney Meadows Primary School were given iPads to use. The Government is still threatening legal action because the AEU won&apos;t suspend work bans. The industrial action planned by teachers includes a statewide strike on February 14.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Flora Nixon, Prep Teacher</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Martin Dixon, Victorian Minister for Education</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Meredith Peace, Australian Education Union</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Naef Ali, Prep Student</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Industrial disputes</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Teachers</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ABC 1 News 30_01_13 school.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="6">
<inm:StationProg>ABC TV News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Ian Henderson</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>19:17 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:03</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Victorian Coroner Jennifer Coate has recommended Victoria ban lane changes in any new road tunnels to avoid a repeat of the fatal crash in the Burnley Tunnel. The coroner ruled a retrofit of the Burnley Tunnel wasn&apos;t practical. The truck driver responsible was sentenced to five years jail.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Terry Mulder, Victorian Minister for Roads</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Road accidents</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Roads - City Link</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ABC 1 News 30_01_13 tunnel crash.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="7">
<inm:StationProg>ABC TV News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Ian Henderson</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>19:14 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:12</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> The cost of household insurance is set to fall as Victoria changes the way it funds its fire fighting effort. From July, insurance companies will face fines of up to ten million dollars if they continue to charge a fire services levy. Council rates will rise, however. Changing the way people pay for fire services from the MFB and CFA was one recommendation from the Bushfires Royal Commission. The Insurance Council of Australia was not available for an interview but told the ABC the change will drive down the cost of policies. Councils aren&apos;t looking forward to putting their rates up. Kim Wells, Victorian Treasurer, has announced $53 million to help local governments deal with the transition. The Victorian Opposition says the Government has bungled the entire process. The Victorian Government says the changes include abolishing the associated GST and stamp duty costs on the old levy which will save more than $100 million for households and businesses.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Allan Fels, Fire Levy Monitor</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Kim Wells, Victorian Treasurer</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Rob Spence, CEO, Municipal Association of Victoria</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Tim Holding, Victorian Shadow  Treasurer</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Fire insurance</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Local Government - Finance</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ABC 1 News 30_01_13 Fire Levy.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="8">
<inm:StationProg>HSV 7 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:25 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:13</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Mitchell welcomes Tony Abbott, Federal Opposition Leader, to talk about the upcoming Australian Federal Election which has been announced by Julia Gillard, Australian Prime Minister, today to be the 14th of September. Abbott says they were ready for the election for a long time and he has already been campaigning on their real solutions plan for the past week. Abbott says Gillard has called the election this early to give them the longest campaign in Australian history. Abbott says they will keep their commitments but will not comment on the funding taken from the Royal Childrens Hospital. Abbott says they will repeal the carbon tax which will mend the Victorian manufacturing industry. Mitchell wonders how often Abbott will be in Speedos during the campaign. Abbott says he will accept the invitation of Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier, to swim in Lorne again.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Tony Abbott, Federal Opposition Leader</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Elections - Australia - Seats</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/HSV 7 News 30_01_13 election.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="9">
<inm:StationProg>HSV 7 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:20 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:27</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> V/Line is trialling new train carriages where passengers are urged to speak and work quietly. Terry Mulder, Victorian Minister for Public Transport and Roads, says there will be quiet carriages running on a number of lines. Ross Pedley, Acting CEO, V/Line, says people are being asked to be respectful.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Marie Beatie, Passenger</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ross Pedley, Acting CEO, V/Line</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Terry Mulder, Victorian Minister for Public Transport and Roads</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Transport - Trains</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Transport policy</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/HSV 7 News 30_01_13 VLine.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="10">
<inm:StationProg>GTV 9 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Hitchener</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:19 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:38</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> A radical push for a blanket ban on smoking in Melbourne&apos;s CBD is facing a few drawbacks. A year ago the idea was put to the public and it failed to win support. Designated smoking areas are being considered as a last resort. Anti-smoking lobby groups believe a full ban won&apos;t work. Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier, recently banned smoking in between flags on beaches.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Councillor Richard Foster, Melbourne City Council</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Dr Stephen Parnis, AMA</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Kylie Lindorff, QUIT</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Neil Wayman, Smoker</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Robert Doyle, Lord Mayor, Melbourne City Council</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Smoking</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Local Government - Regulations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/GTV 9 News 30_01_13 smoking.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="11">
<inm:StationProg>GTV 9 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Hitchener</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:18 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:26</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> A coroner has recommended emergency lanes be included in future road tunnels and a ban on lane changes following the Burnley Tunnel tragedy in 2007. Driver David Kalwig was jailed for five years. The Victorian Government says changes to the existing tunnel system have already been made and they will use the recommendations as a guide for tunnel construction.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee />
<inm:Subject>Road accidents</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Roads - City Link</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Coronial enquiries</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/GTV 9 News 30_01_13 tunnel crash.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="12">
<inm:StationProg>HSV 7 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:15 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:50</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Thousands of prep students in Victoria have gone to school for the first time today. Bernadette Curry, Mother , says her average supermarket visit costs $400 and shoes cost $650. Greg Parr, Spokesperson, Victoria Police, says they caught a P Plater speeding.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Bernadette Curry</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Mother</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Greg Parr, Spokesperson, Victoria Police</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>School speed zones</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>School fees</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/HSV 7 News 30_01_13 schools.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="13">
<inm:StationProg>HSV 7 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:09 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:44</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> A Coroner has recommended a ban on lane changes in the Burnley Tunnel in her review of the accident in 2007 which claimed the lives of three people. The coroner has also suggest to VicRoads there should be emergency stopping bays in any future tunnel being built. Terry Mulder, Victorian Minister for Public Transport and Roads, says they will take the recommendations on board.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Terry Mulder, Victorian Minister for Public Transport and Roads</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Coronial enquiries</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Road accidents</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Roads - City Link</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/HSV 7 News 30_01_13 tunnel crash.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="14">
<inm:StationProg>GTV 9 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Hitchener</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:05 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:28</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Several Victorian seats will hold the key to the next election but PM Julia Gillard is already battling controversy over the timing of the poll. The Liberals are keen to pinch the seat of Anna Burke, Member for Chisholm. Ironically, Victorian Government MPs were meeting to plan the year ahead when the election was called. Although election campaigns are traditionally bad for business, industry leaders have been calling for a poll date to end uncertainty. Some in the Jewish community are upset because September 14 is Yom Kippur. The election will be right in the middle of AFL finals. Former Geelong player Cameron Mooney tweeted his disappointment about the timing. The seats to watch are Deakin, Corangamite, La Trobe, Aston, Dunkley and Melbourne. Former Victorian Premier Jeff Kennett lost power last time a September election was held.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Julia Gillard, Australian Prime Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Nina Bassat, Jewish Community Council</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Peter Anderson, Chamber of Commerce</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>vox pops</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Elections - Australia - Seats</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/GTV 9 News 30_01_13 election date.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="15">
<inm:StationProg>HSV 7 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:03 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:53</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> The state of Victoria will be crucial for Julia Gillard, Australian Prime Minister, and the Labor party with two of the parties seats held with margins of less than one percent. Vox pops from the electorate of Gillard discuss whether or not they like her in comparison to Tony Abbott, Federal Opposition Leader. One man says he would prefer Malcolm Turnbull, Federal Shadow Minister for Communications and Broadband, to Abbott. Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier, says he has support for Abbott. Colin Rubinstein, Spokesperson Jewish Affairs Council, says many will use postal votes.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Colin Rubinstein, Spokesperson Jewish Affairs Council</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Vox Pops</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Elections - Australia - Seats</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/HSV 7 News 30_01_13 election date.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="16">
<inm:StationProg>ATV 10 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Mal Walden</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:38 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:33</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> 75,000 Victorians are starting school for the first time tomorrow. The generation is replacing notepads with iPads. One classroom has four sets of twins at St Phillip&apos;s Primary School in Blackburn. Families will now miss out on the $300 School Start Bonus as part of the Victorian Government&apos;s budget cuts. Victorian Opposition Leader Daniel Andrews says the cuts target the most disadvantaged students across the state. Victorian Education Minister Martin Dixon says they&apos;ve increased the Education Maintenance Allowance for eligible children. There will be heavy police patrols in school zones.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Martin Dixon, Victorian Minister for Education</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Raquelle Pearce, Mother</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Unnamed twins</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>School speed zones</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>School students</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ATV 10 News 30_01_13 schools.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="17">
<inm:StationProg>ATV 10 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Mal Walden</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:37 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:30</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Loud phone calls and electronic interruptions are being banned on selected V/Line train trips. Victorian Transport Minister Terry Mulder has announced the arrival of quiet carriages on seven country trains.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Terry Mulder, Victorian Minister for Public Transport and Roads</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Transport - Trains</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Transport policy</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ATV 10 News 30_01_13 VLine.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="18">
<inm:StationProg>ATV 10 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Mal Walden</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:27 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:26</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Insurance companies have been put on notice to do the right thing over Victoria&apos;s new Fire Services Levy or face huge fines. The new system hits people without home insurance. Professor Alan Fels has insurance companies in his sights. The cost of the Fire Services Levy will be shifted to Councils from July 1, with a saving of about $50. There will be a $10m fine for insurers found double-dipping. The uninsured will now have to pay $60m through their council rates. Vic Treasurer Kim Wells says the new system is fair and equitable. The exact cost of the levy will be released in the May budget, giving councils just six weeks to organise the first payments. Rob Spence, Municipal Association of Victoria, says councils are unhappy about collecting the levy.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Campbell Fuller, Insurance Council of Australia</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Kim Wells, Victorian Treasurer</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Professor Alan Fels, Fire Services Levy Monitor</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Rob Spence, Municipal Association of Victoria</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Fire insurance</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Local Government - Finance</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ATV 10 News 30_01_13 Fire Levy.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="19">
<inm:StationProg>ATV 10 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Mal Walden</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:25 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:13</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Six years after a horror Burnley Tunnel crash killed three people, a coroner has called for lane changes to be banned in future tunnels. The accident was sparked when truck driver David Kalwig swerved to avoid another truck that had broken down in the tunnel. Former Olympic cyclist Damian McDonald, Darren Sporn and Geoffrey Kennard died in the accident. Kalwig was jailed for dangerous driving more than three years ago. Victorian Transport Minister Terry Mulder says the coroner&apos;s recommendations will be taken into consideration by the Linking Melbourne Authority, particularly for the new East-West Link. The report places no blame on either of the three victims, or authorities responsible for the Burnley Tunnel. Justice Coate accepts previous court findings that Kalwig&apos;s reckless driving led to the tragedy.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Terry Mulder, Victorian Minister for Public Transport and Roads</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Road accidents</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Roads - City Link</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ATV 10 news 30_01_13 Tunnel crash.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="20">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Rafael Epstein</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>16:55 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>3:19</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Continued regular segment Fight Club with Labor Senator David Feeney and Liberal MP Josh Frydenberg. Epstein asks if there is any disadvantage is announcing an election so late. Feeney says it is not, as everyone knew the Federal Government would call the election late in the year. Epstein asks how can the Federal Government resolve the health problem with Victoria. Feeney says the Commonwealth Grants Process assists the State Government&apos;s manage their health systems and the funding has risen dramatically despite recent cuts. Feeney says the Victorian Government have more responsibility to resolve their funding problems. Frydenberg says Tony Abbott wants to devolve more authority to local hospital boards to give them more of a say. Frydenberg says the Federal Government have greatly cut health and education funding which is causing all the problems. Frydenberg says this is because of the private health insurance rebate and the failing dental scheme which is hurting Victoria.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>David Feeney, Labor Senator</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee> Josh Frydenberg, Liberal MP</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Federal State Financial Relations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Health Care - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Hospital funding</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Drive 30_01_13 FightClub.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="21">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Tom Elliott</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>15:11 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>3:45</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Interview with Professor Mike Daube, Australian Council on Smoking and Health. Daube discusses the Perth City Council&apos;s overnight decision to ban smoking in outside malls. Daube says there is tremendous public support and awareness of the dangers of smoking, saying that most smokers want to quit anyway. Daube says an idea would be to ban the sale of cigarettes to people born after a certain date. Daube says there should be a question over tobacco sale outlets. Daube says Victoria is behind other states on cigarette restrictions, noting the Victorian Government has reduced its Quit funding. Daube says we should not ban cigarettes overnight but should perhaps set an end date. Daube says he does not think alcohol is very far behind, but that it is different to smoking. Daube says cigarettes are harmful and even lethal if used as intended. Daube says the focus on alcohol should be towards encouraging sensible drinking and changing the culture of drinking to get drunk.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Professor Mike Daube, Australian Council on Smoking and Health</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Smoking</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Local Government - Regulations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 30_01_13 Daube.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="22">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Denis Walter</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>12:22 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:20</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Interview with Terry Mulder, Victorian Minister for Public Transport, to discuss calls for a quiet carriage on trains. Mulder says V/Line will be conducting a trial over a six month period. He says the trial will alternate between the Ballarat, Bendigo, Geelong and Traralgon lines. He says the system works successfully in Qld and is based on respect.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Terry Mulder, Victorian Minister for Public Transport</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Transport - Trains</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Transport policy</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Afternoons 30_01_13 Mulder.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="23">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>30 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:22 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>7:07</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Interview with Tony Abbott, Federal Opposition Leader. Mitchell says Tony Abbott, Federal Opposition Leader, is on a mini campaign around Australia. He says the PM is addressing the National Press Club today, and it is believed she will target &apos;middle class welfare&apos;. He notes Abbott has just been up to the Peter MacCallum Cancer Centre. He says they broke the news last week that the Centre were closing beds due to a funding dispute between the State Victorian and Federal Governments. He says every hospital is affected by the dispute. He asks if Abbott is elected would he put funding into the &apos;Peter Mac&apos; to ensure beds don&apos;t close. Abbott says he would like to ensure they are opening beds not closing them. He says he hopes today the PM will tell us the true state of the nation&apos;s books, and once she does that they will be in a better position to say what commitments they can make. He confirms he can&apos;t guarantee to return the funding. He agrees that it is an &apos;indecent battle&apos;. He says both Kevin Rudd and Julia Gillard said they would end the &apos;blame game&apos; but it is worse than ever. He says the cuts to hospitals came half way through the financial year. He denies that the Baillieu Victorian Government have made cuts, noting they have made &apos;rationalisations and efficiencies&apos;. He says all savings have been reinvested in Victoria&apos;s public hospitals. He says since the change of government there has been a $1.3b increase in hospital funding.
Mitchell asks about the proposed anti discrimination laws, giving an example of not liking Indian food. Abbott guarantees to repeal the laws if they go through. He talks about Indian food. He says the last thing the country needs is further restrictions on free speech. He discusses food he likes. He answers a question about swimming down the Yarra with Ted Baillieu Victorian Premier, noting they both did the Lorne swim last year. He confirms he would swim in the Yarra for a good cause, noting it is important to clean it up.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Tony Abbott, Federal Opposition Leader</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Elections - Australia - Policies</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Hospital funding</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Federal State Financial Relations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 30_01_13 Abbott.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="24">
<inm:StationProg>ABC TV News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Ian Henderson</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>19:21 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:54</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> The former headquarters of The Age newspaper will soon be demolished to make way for new apartments. The Victorian Government has approved an $800M redevelopment of the site. Matthew Guy, Planning Minister says the development is exciting for the city.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Matthew Guy, Planning Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Planning - Melbourne</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Property Development - Melbourne</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ABC 1 News 29_01_13 Guy.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="25">
<inm:StationProg>ABC TV News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Ian Henderson</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>19:14 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:54</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Collingwood President Eddie Maguire says he has no idea if reports that some players have confessed to illicit drug use are true. News Limited is suggesting that at least four Collingwood players have informed the AFL&apos;s medical department about their drug use. Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier says that it needs to be made sure the drug testing is effective. Collingwood are pushing for change at the drug summit tomorrow.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Dyson Heppell, Essendon</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Eddie McGuire, Collingwood President</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Sport - AFL</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Drug abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ABC 1 News 29_01_13 AFL drugs.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="26">
<inm:StationProg>HSV 7 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:40 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:28</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Sports report Tennis - Australian Open officials will work with the Victorian Government to avoid a repeat of Saturday night, when the Australia Day fireworks interrupted the women&apos;s final. Victorian Premier Ted Baillieu says we can&apos;t have an international event stop for local fireworks.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Sport - National Tennis Centre</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/HSV 7 News 29_01_13 Tennis.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="27">
<inm:StationProg>GTV 9 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Hitchener</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:22 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:32</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> The former home of The Age newspaper will be demolished to make way for skyscrapers. Sean Hogan, ISPT Property says that nobody is a fan of the building. The Victorian Government has approved plans for six high rise towers on the street. Matthew Guy, Planning Minister says it is the end of an era. The development will include almost 3000 apartments with developers saying it will transform the west end of the city. Construction may take eight to twelve years.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Matthew Guy, Planning Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Sean Hogan, ISPT Property</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Planning - Melbourne</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Property Development - Melbourne</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/GTV 9 News 29_01_13 The Age building.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="28">
<inm:StationProg>GTV 9 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Hitchener</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:21 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:35</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Taxpayers have been forced to spend $8M so that peak hour trains can stop at Cardinia Station. Terry Mulder, Transport Minister says the power supplies should have been in place and a new sub station opened today solving the problem.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Terry Mulder, Transport Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Transport - Trains</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Transport infrastructure</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Railway stations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/GTV 9 News 29_01_13 Mulder.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="29">
<inm:StationProg>HSV 7 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:20 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:46</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> The Baillieu Government has flatly rejected calls from Monash University lecturer Dr David Zyngier to radically alter the school calendar. The idea is for students to avoid going to school in the hot month of February. Some parents did not agree with the proposals. The Australian Education Union says that Dr Zyngier highlights the need for a good learning environment. James Merlino, Shadow Education Minister, called for more investment in education. Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier, ruled out the changes. Martin Dixon, Victorian Minister for Education, says that the next five years worth of dates are set in stone.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Alex Hill, Father</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Catherine Curlas, Nanny</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Charlie, School Student</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Dr David Zyngier, Lecturer, Monash University</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>James Merlino, Shadow Education Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Malcolm Hill, Grandfather</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Martin Dixon, Victorian Minister for Education</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Meredith Peace, Spokesperson, Australian Education Union</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>School terms</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/HSV 7 News 29_01_13 school terms.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="30">
<inm:StationProg>GTV 9 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Hitchener</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:15 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:40</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Parents have reacted unfavourably to a proposal for schools to return in March to beat the summer heat. Dr David Zyngier, Monash University says that this time of year is too hot and he has the support of the Victorian Principals Association. Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier says the plan will probably not get off the ground.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Dr David Zyngier, Monash University</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Gabrielle Leigh, Victorian Principals Association</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Jackson Sandford, Student</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Sam Sandford, Parent</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>School terms</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/GTV 9 News 29_01_13 school terms.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="31">
<inm:StationProg>GTV 9 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Hitchener</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:09 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:45</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> At least four Collingwood AFL players have allegedly confessed to drug use, in a bid to exploit a loop hole in the AFL&apos;s drug policy. The admission comes ahead of tomorrow&apos;s AFL drug summit. Eddie McGuire, Collingwood President says as far as he knows there has never been a problem and he wants a new drug code. Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier has said that it needs to be an effective change to drug policy. The drug summit tomorrow will include medical experts and police.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Dyson Heppell, Essendon</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Eddie McGuire, Collingwood President</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Jarrad Waite, Carlton</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Sport - AFL</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Drug abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/GTV 9 news 30_01_13 AFL drugs.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="32">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Tom Elliott</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:39 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>4:39</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Elliott says the Victorian Health Minister David Davis says the Federal Government took $106m from his health budget whilst the Federal Health Minister Tanya Plibersek says Davis took out over $600m. Elliott says he doesn&apos;t know where Plibersek got her figure from. Interview with Tom Wilson, former Health Department bureaucrat. Wilson says his letter in The Age is nothing to do with the finger pointing between the Federal Government and the Victorian Government. Wilson says private enterprise needs to be factored into the issue of health. Wilson says things such as Government&apos;s making contracts with private hospitals to do certain sorts of surgery instead of waiting for a position to become available in a public hospital needs to be looked into. Wilson says $35b would need to be spent in the next ten years to make adequate health infrastructure which was rejected obviously by treasury. Wilson says budget allocations in Victoria are around 1/5 of this. Wilson says renal specialists have put together dialysis centres and there is a women&apos;s health facility on Burwood Road that provides adequate health. Wilson says people with private health insurance should not be allowed into the public health system.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Tom Wilson, former Health Department bureaucrat</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Federal State Financial Relations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Health Care - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Hospital funding</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Drive 29_01_13 Wilson.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="33">
<inm:StationProg>ATV 10 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Mal Walden</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:38 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:36</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> School is back for more than 800,000 Victorian students. Preparations have been over-shadowed, with frustrated teachers still at loggerheads with the Victorian Government over a pay dispute. A proposal to start school in March has won support from some. Victorian Premier Ted Baillieu says the proposition has never gotten off the ground, and doesn&apos;t think it will now. Thousands of state schools are soon to be given time off when teachers again take their pay claim to the streets, despite a resumption in negotiations on Thursday. There is concern the ongoing dispute will delay the roll out of a national curriculum in Victoria. Motorists have been warned to slow down in school zones.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Meredith Peace, Australian Education Union</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Vox pops, students</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Industrial disputes</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Teachers</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ATV 10 news 30_01_13 Teachers.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="34">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Rafael Epstein</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:35 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>9:00</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Interview with Matthew Guy, Victorian Minister for Planning who has approved an $800m development of 3000 apartments on the old Age building site in Spencer Street. Guy confirms another development has been approved on the Upper West Side Development. Guy says they and the Victorian Government have been working to encourage development in that area of the CBD to remove demand on suburban transport infrastructure. Guy says the Savoy Hotel site on Spencer St is a complete eyesore, and talks about the application process, the developer&apos;s obligations and the role of the City of Melbourne. Guy says that the project is backed by ISPT, and adds that the high density market in Melbourne is stronger than in other parts of Australia. Epstein asks whether the Royal Melbourne and the Children&apos;s Hospital will receive more money to cope with the added amount of people living in the city. Epstein asks where the children of the families living in the area will go to school. Guy says the Victorian Government are in discussions to develop schools in the area, which the previous Victorian Labor Government failed to do. Guy says a Robo Poll did not show the ALP ahead of the Victorian Coalition, adding that Bob Carr was behind in the polls as Premier and ended up winning the next election. Guy says he does not intend to challenge Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier for the leadership.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Matthew Guy, Victorian Minister for Planning</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Property Development - Melbourne</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Planning - Melbourne</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Drive 29_01_13 Guy.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="35">
<inm:StationProg>ATV 10 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Mal Walden</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:10 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:47</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> In a huge blow to the AFL&apos;s tough stance on drugs, claims have emerged that players have found a loophole to beat its three-strike policy. The damaging revelations will be top of the agenda at tomorrow&apos;s drug summit. At least four Collingwood Magpies players are believed to have contacted an AFL Medical Officer about drug use last year. It was a surprise for an angry President Eddie McGuire. McGuire says it&apos;s supposed to be confidential, and the Club doesn&apos;t receive information about specific cases. Vic Premier Ted Baillieu says the AFL needs to ensure its system is loophole-free and effective. Players from other clubs are also believed to have made their own self-reports. Sydney Coach John Longmire says he&apos;s looking forward to seeing what comes out of tomorrow&apos;s drugs summit. The League chose not to comment today.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Eddie McGuire, President, Collingwood Football Club</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Jarrad Waite, Player, Carlton Football Club</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>John Longmire, Coach, Sydney Swans Football Club</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Nathan Buckley, Coach, Collingwood Football Club</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Sport - AFL</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Drug abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ATV 10 news 30_01_13 AFL drugs.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="36">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Tom Elliott</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:08 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>6:59</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Elliott says Federation of Community Legal Centres Victoria&apos;s Hugh de Kretser wrote an opinion piece in The Age, taking aim at Victorian Premier Ted Baillieu&apos;s PSO initiative to implement armed protective services officers at train stations. Elliott says de Kretser argued PSOs should not have guns, that batons and capsicum spray was enough, and that they should really be Transport Police rather than PSOs. Elliott says de Kretser argued violence could go up under PSOs as someone could accidentally be shot.  Interview with Hugh de Kretser, Federation of Community Legal Centres Victoria. de Kretser discusses his article in The Age taking aim at the Victorian Government&apos;s PSO system, saying that the article pointed out there was a genuine safety perception problem on public transport at night. de Kretser says there is a gap between this perception and actual safety, with the currently policy inflexibly applying two PSOs to each station regardless of threat to safety. Elliott says if something was to happen it would be difficult for the Victorian Premier to explain there were no PSOs due to a low risk environment. de Kretser says that there is a case for increased Victoria Police or PSO presence at some stations, such as Frankston, Dandenong, Sunshine and Flinders St, not just at night but from the first train until the last train. de Kretser says Victoria Police are overrepresented when it comes to fatal shootings, especially involving those with mental illness, and placing two armed PSOs on each train station could increase the risk of this happening. de Kretser says he supports Police having guns and notes he is concerned about the lack of experience for PSOs. Elliott says Police do not draw their gun often but there are situations where it is necessary.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Hugh de Kretser, Federation of Community Legal Centres Victoria</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Protective Services Officers</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Public transport safety</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Drive 29_01_13 DeKrester.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="37">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Rafael Epstein</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>15:06 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>8:35</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Epstein says some teachers and students may have been disappointed when Rock Eisteddfod Challenge finished. Epstein welcomes Wakakirri national festival director Adam Loxley, who explains since 1992 it has aimed to help primary school children learn through creating and sharing stories. Loxley says they contacted Victorian Youth Affairs Minister Ryan Smith and got Victorian Government funding for at least two years. Loxley says a public meeting is on 15 February, Wakakirri is booked at Melbourne Convention Centre and he discusses the influence of Glee.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Adam Loxley, Director, Wakakirri Festival</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Music festivals</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Drive 29_01_13 Loxley.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="38">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Jon Faine</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>10:38 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:27</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Faine says he earlier discussed the idea of hospitals admitting adults into children&apos;s wards. Faine says David Davis, Victorian Health Minister, claims he is uncomfortable with this idea and he was not aware of it being a widespread practise. Faine says he&apos;s confirmed one of the hospitals in the Southern Health network is doing this. Faine says he&apos;s received reports from Northern Health and Ballarat of this occurring. Faine finds this practise odd. Faine says there&apos;s a chance of a breakthrough when Davis and Tanya Plibersek [Federal Health Minister] meet on Friday. Faine says Federal Greens Senator, Richard Di Natale, is calling for an inquiry into hospital funding. Faine says PM Julia Gillard&apos;s partner, Tim Mathieson, has attracted criticism for making a politically incorrect speech about prostate cancer. Faine says Gillard did not laugh at this joke. Faine says Ita Buttrose believes Mathieson should be in hot water for his comments.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee />
<inm:Subject>Health Care - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Federal State Financial Relations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Hospital funding</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Mornings 29_01_13 Health and Asian digits.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="39">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:32 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>5:25</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Mitchell is joined by Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier. Baillieu says the fireworks for Australia Day are not good for the Australian Open and it doesn&apos;t work. Caller, Michelle, says she owns a school camp at King Lake. She says they rebuilt after the bushfires. She says because of the industrial dispute between the government and education department, she has had five camps cancelled. Baillieu says it was a decision by the union to escalate industrial action. He says the government believes the action is unlawful. He says it is this disruption to families and students that is inappropriate. Mitchell says Peter Garrett, Federal Schools Minister, wants it sorted because the national curriculum cannot be introduced until it is.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Michelle</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Education - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Teachers - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Industrial Relations - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Industrial disputes</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Education - Curriculum</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 29_01_13 Baillieu10.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="40">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:29 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:22</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier. Mitchell asks why the Victorian government has been extremely critical of anti-discrimination laws the federal government have proposed. Baillieu says they are a step too far. He notes they have made representations, as have the Attorney-General. He predicts they will not go ahead as proposed. Mitchell suggests if someone is offended by something &apos;you are in strife&apos;. Baillieu agrees it could be interpreted that way. Mitchell refers to comments made by the PM&apos;s partner, Tim Mathieson, at The Lodge. Mitchell plays an excerpt of Tim Mathieson. Baillieu says Mathieson was talking about a great cause but used a poor choice of words. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Tim Mathieson, Julia Gillard&apos;s partner [excerpt]</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Law reform</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Freedom of speech</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Men&apos;s health</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Cancer</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Political correctness</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 29_01_13 Baillieu9.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="41">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:29 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:29</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier. Mitchell asks if the Peninsula Link is big enough. Baillieu notes he heard it was under pressure, following the Australia Day weekend yesterday. He says perhaps the Nepean Highway and the Moorooduc were available [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Roads - Melbourne</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Freeways</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Traffic management</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Traffic congestion</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 29_01_13 Baillieu8.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="42">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:24 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>4:47</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier. Mitchell notes the AFL has a drug conference tomorrow and asks if it is time they did away with the three strike policy. Baillieu commends the AFL for the action on drugs. He discusses their action, and the players reactions. He notes that Victoria Police and the transport industry also drug test. He discusses his government&apos;s action on drug testing. He talks about the issue of self reporting in the AFL. Baillieu discusses the potential for drug and alcohol testing for politicians, in response to a question by Mitchell. He talks about changes in alcohol use and smoking in parliament in his own time. Mitchell asks if he would agree to random testing if Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader, agreed to it. Baillieu says they are keen to set standards [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Sport - AFL</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Drugs in sport</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 29_01_13 Baillieu7.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="43">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:23 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:52</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier. Mitchell says the Australian Industry Group is today reporting that Victorian businesses are paying 17% more for electricity since the carbon tax came in. He notes that the Baillieu Government was &apos;damning&apos; about what the carbon tax would do to Victoria and asks if it has &apos;been a bit of a fizzer&apos;. Baillieu says it has hit businesses, hospitals, and schools [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Cost Of Living - Prices</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Electricity Prices</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Budget - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Carbon taxes</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 29_01_13 Baillieu6.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="44">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:22 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:00</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier. Caller, Julie, says prior to the election, Baillieu stated that PSOs would be on stations from first train until the last train, not 6pm onwards. Baillieu denies this, saying they made it very clear it would be 6pm until last train. Julie says that is not what Terry Mulder said. Baillieu reiterates that the policy was clear and they said 6pm until last train. Julie asks why PSOs are only being placed on &apos;manned&apos; stations, when stations where there is trouble are often stations which are not premium. Baillieu says she is not describing it correctly, and says the [Victoria Police] Chief Commissioner decides where they go, based on the appropriateness of the roll-out [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Julie</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Public transport safety</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Railway stations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Protective Services Officers</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 29_01_13 Baillieu5.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="45">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:16 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:51</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier. Mitchell refers to a proposal by a Monash University professor regarding potential changes to school holidays. Baillieu denies they are considering the proposal. He notes that air conditioning should be provided in some schools. He discusses his own experience designing schools. He refers to BER projects. He notes there is currently funding coming out of Victorian schools due to the carbon tax. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Federal State Financial Relations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Education - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Schools</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>School terms</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>School funding</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 29_01_13 Baillieu4.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="46">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:14 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:07</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier. Mitchell says the latest poll says they will be beaten in the next state election. Baillieu says there are significant economic challenges to in Victoria and they have been making tough decisions. He discusses their focus. Mitchell says the perception is they are the &apos;do nothing government&apos;. Baillieu denies this, saying they have done what they said they would do. He says they have introduced PSOs on train stations, cut stamp duty, extended energy concessions, provided cuts to ambulance subscriptions, provided more police, put more train services in place and have a record infrastructure spend in place. He says they have introduced significant reforms regarding the fire services levy and the Broad Based Anti-Corruption Commission [IBAC]. He refuses to discuss whey they are unpopular [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Baillieu Government</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Government inaction</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Political polling</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 29_01_13 Baillieu3.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="47">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:11 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:20</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier. Caller, Brian, says teachers are going back to school and asks how performance based pay will work. Baillieu says the intention is to provide schools with the opportunity to reward teachers according to performance. He says it will give 70% of teachers with an opportunity to receive performance paid bonuses. He discusses the percentages. Brian asks about the impacts of a teacher who has a class that &apos;doesn&apos;t make the grade&apos;. Baillieu says common sense will prevail and the principal will take it into account. Mitchell asks about court action against the teachers. Baillieu says they have said if the AEU continue with industrial action, they will pursue it in the Federal Court. He notes he thinks there will be talks tomorrow or Thursday [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Brian</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Education - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Teachers - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Industrial Relations - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Industrial disputes</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 29_01_13 Baillieu2.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="48">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Neil Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:08 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>3:34</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Interview with Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier. Mitchell says he saw Baillieu with Julia Gillard, Australian Prime Minister, in the bushfire zone. He asks if they talked about the hospital crisis. Baillieu denies that they did, noting Gillard made it clear to the media and others she thought it was an inappropriate time to be talking about other issues. He confirms he was keen to discuss it, but didn&apos;t want to &apos;create a stunt&apos;. He says he has written to the PM and has invited her to have a briefing from their health department. He says he can only assume she is misinformed, as to assume otherwise would mean she is deliberately misleading Victorians. He notes the hospital funding cut, announced by the Commonwealth, was announced in November and he is staggered that they are seeking to deny they are responsible for the cuts. Mitchell says there is a &apos;blame game&apos; going on around sick people. Baillieu reiterates he was prepared to talk to Gillard. He notes the PM flew in to Sale and he flew in to Heyfield. They had time on the ground with those involved in the fire. Mitchell says his minister suggested the situation could cost lives if it is not sorted out. Baillieu discusses the cuts in funding and the impact on patients. He refuses to say the cuts will cost lives, but says the situation comes with risk [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Health Care - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Federal State Financial Relations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Hospital funding</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 29_01_13 Baillieu1.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="49">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Jon Faine</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>08:52 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>3:00</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Dr Richard Di Natale, Federal Greens Senator. Faine explains Di Natale is calling for an inquiry into health funding and the responsibilities of governments. Di Natale says he has no indication whether the other parties will support it and explains it is an opportunity. He says people waiting to get their hip done don&apos;t want to hear politicians blame each other. Di Natale is describes how they want to develop more lasting solutions. Faine claims Kevin Rudd was going to end the blame game and whenever governments change, they say they will fix things, but end up going around in circles. Di Natale calls for the Senate to come up with recommendations. He says government needs to provide education for kids, health care and the environment. Faine says the politics will never be taken from out of it. Di Natale explains a Senate inquiry is an opportunity for submissions from stakeholders and groups across party lines. He says the changes were made at the wrong time and the Victorian government ripped out millions from the system, so give and take is needed from both sides.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Dr Richard Di Natale, Federal Greens Senator</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Health Care - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Federal State Financial Relations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Hospital funding</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Mornings 29_01_13 Richard Di Natale.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="50">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Jon Faine</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>08:44 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:39</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with David Davis, Victorian Health Minister. Faine explains the joke by Tim Mathieson, at a Lodge function for cricketers, about prostate examinations. Faine says he has a deluge of texts and callers on it. Davis says he saw it last night and winced and claims it was not the right thing to say. He says the deeper message about cancer was good, but was delivered in an unfortunate way. Davis says the PM&apos;s face said it all.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>David Davis, Victorian Health Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Tim Matheson, Julia Gillard&apos;s partner [excerpt]</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Men&apos;s health</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Cancer</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Political correctness</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Mornings 29_01_13 Davis3.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="51">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Jon Faine</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>08:42 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:24</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with David Davis, Victorian Health Minister. Faine says there will be a meeting with the Federal Health Minister, Tanya Plibersek. Davis confirms this will be on Friday at the airport. Davis says the Baillieu Government had sought an earlier meeting at a health service so the minister could see the impact of cuts. Davis says this was discussed previously in Perth when all six minister made it clear none of them supported what the Commonwealth had done and requested Treasury revisit calculations. Faine says even Labor states SA and Tasmania agreed. Davis confirms this. Davis says there has been commentary on the population basis and says they have explained the basis for the decision is flawed as the population is growing and suggests the Greens may look at it. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>David Davis, Victorian Health Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Health Care - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Federal State Financial Relations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Hospital funding</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Mornings 29_01_13 Davis2.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="52">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Jon Faine</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>29 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>08:40 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:02</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Interview with David Davis, Victorian Health Minister. Faine asks if Davis has heard of adults in children&apos;s wards. Davis says it might happen at time to time and says the Southern Health policy is not to have children with adults. Faine says they are breaching that. Davis says an eighteen year old was in a ward with younger people. Faine says there were older people. Davis distinguishes between small and large health services. Faine says in Ballarat, the children&apos;s ward has adults in there as does Northern Health. Davis explains his staff have spoken to Southern Health. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>David Davis, Victorian Health Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Health Care - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Hospitals</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Children&apos;s health</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Mornings 29_01_13 Davis1.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="53">
<inm:StationProg>ABC TV News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Ian Henderson</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>19:14 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:54</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Julia Gillard, Australian Prime Minister and Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier, toured fire affected areas of Gippsland to lend their support to residents and fire crews. One man died and twenty-one homes were destroyed by the Aberfeldy fire. The leaders were briefed with emergency service officials at Heyfield and headed to Seaton to see the damage. They joined CFA volunteers for morning tea and thanked them for their efforts.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Julia Gillard, Australian PM</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Emergency services</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Fire brigades</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Bushfires</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ABC 1 News 28_01_13 Julia tours Gipps.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="54">
<inm:StationProg>ATV 10 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Carrie Bickmore, Charlie Pickering, Gorgi Coghlan and Steve Price</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:46 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:19</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Julia Gillard, Australian Prime Minister and Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier, have today visited bushfire-affected Gippsland. The blaze near Seaton and Heyfield claimed the life of one man and destroyed more than twenty homes.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee />
<inm:Subject>Emergency services</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Fire brigades</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Bushfires</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title>The Project</inm:Title>
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ATV 10 News The Project 28_01_13 Fires.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="55">
<inm:StationProg>SBS TV News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Anton Enus and Janice Petersen</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:44 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:17</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Authorities in Victoria are warning against complacency, as conditions continue to favour crews managing the prevailing bushfire threat. There are three main fires causing concern, the most recent at Violet Town. Prime Minister Julia Gillard was today briefed at the Heyfield Incident Control Centre. Gillard and Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier, met locals in Gippsland and toured the incident control centre. Violet Town residents were today told that a favourable wind change has given the sixty trucks and helicopters attacking the blaze the upper hand. Another blaze at Harrietville has also eased. Andrew Bennet, Department of Sustainability and Environment [DSE] spokesman, is asking people to maintain awareness of the current fire situation through the Victorian Bushfire Information Line, the DSE website, or local radio.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Andrew Bennet, DSE spokesman</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Julia Gillard, Australian Prime Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Emergency services</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Fire brigades</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Bushfires</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/SBS 1 News 28_01_12 Gippsland fires.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="56">
<inm:StationProg>HSV 7 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:21 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:31</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>The Yarra River has recorded unacceptably high bacteria levels. Anglers are throwing their catch back into the water and rowers are worried about falling in, with fears for their health. Parts of the river have recorded unacceptably high levels of E. coli, with areas around South Yarra and Abbotsford having levels 85 times higher than those recommended for swimming. At Launching Place, it was 17 times higher. The Victorian government has recently pledged $1 billion, over five years, to help clean up the river.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Geoff Haslam, rower</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Matt Vincent, Environment Protection Authority [EPA] spokesman</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Michael Hawkins, angler</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Yarra River</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Pollution - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/HSV 7 News 28_01_13 Yarra River.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="57">
<inm:StationProg>GTV 9 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Hitchener</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:18 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:34</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>There are renewed calls to clean up the Yarra, with E. Coli in some parts 85 times the safe levels. However, authorities maintain the river is improving. Ian Penrose, Yarra River Keeper Association spokesman, says if people ingest the water when swimming, there is a risk that they will get sick. The bacteria gets in via storm water and Melbourne&apos;s ageing sewerage system. Abbotsford, South Yarra, Healesville and Docklands recorded the worst levels. Melbourne Water takes 70% of its supply from the river in an average year and the EPA says the water is cleaner than ten years ago. Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier, says we would like it to be even cleaner. The Victorian government has promised a clean up. Matt Vincent, Environment Protection Authority [EPA] spokesman, says people need to respect the river.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ian Penrose, Yarra River Keeper Association spokesman</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Janet Reynolds, Kew resident</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Matt Vincent, EPA spokesman</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Vox pops</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Yarra River</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Pollution - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/GTV 9 News 28_01_13 Dirty Yarra.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="58">
<inm:StationProg>GTV 9 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Hitchener</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:14 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:56</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Fire hit areas in Gippsland have received a visit from Australian Prime Minister, Julia Gillard and Victorian Premier, Ted Baillieu, who thanked DSE and CFA volunteers. Gillard says the bushfire risk is not over. Hundreds of trees still need clearing and thousands of fence posts need repair, along with the damage to buildings.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Dianne Dennis, local resident</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Julia Gillard, Australian Prime Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Thayer Lukjanov, volunteer</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Vox pops</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Emergency services</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Fire brigades</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Bushfires</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/GTV 9 News 28_01_13 Gippsland fires.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="59">
<inm:StationProg>HSV 7 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:12 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:44</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Gippsland residents left devastated by bushfire have been offered words of comfort by the Prime Minster and Victorian Premier. The massive Aberfeldy fire will continue to burn for at least the next month, with another large blaze causing headaches in the state&apos;s north-east. The Prime Minister and the premier came to Seaton to see the effects of the Aberfeldy fire and the impact on the locals. The massive Aberfeldy blaze has so far scorched more than 70,000 hectares and its northern edge still provides a major threat. The battle against the Aberfeldy fire is expected to go beyond another month. Dozens of firefighters, two aircraft and bulldozers were on duty today. No deadline has been set for fire-affected residents to claim government support, including hardship grants. A separate blaze in the north-east of Victoria has covered 16000 hectares and last night caused the evacuation of locals in Boho.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Di Dennis, local resident</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Julia Gillard, Australian Prime Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Emergency services</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Fire brigades</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Bushfires</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/HSV 7 News 28_01_13 Ted tours Gippsland.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="60">
<inm:StationProg>ATV 10 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Mal Walden</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:21 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:33</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier, says the Yarra River is a lot cleaner than it used to be, but the Victorian government would like it to be even cleaner. High risk areas are closest to the city. Unsafe swimming levels have been reported at nine locations. Litter, sewerage and animal waste are the major contributors. The Yarra River Keeper Association says leaking sewerage pipes need to be fixed.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ian Penrose, Yarra River Keeper Association spokesman</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Vox pops</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Yarra River</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Pollution - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ATV 10 News 28_01_13 Yarra River.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="61">
<inm:StationProg>ATV 10 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Mal Walden</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:10 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:43</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Julia Gillard joins Victorian Premier, Ted Baillieu, touring bushfire ravaged Gippsland. Locals seemed pleased to see the leaders. Many fire fighters had been battling the Aberfeldy blaze for more than a week. Baillieu says there are other fires burning in Victoria. CFA hopes cooler weather will help their efforts this week.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Dianne Dennis, Seaton resident</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Julia Gillard, Australian PM</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Emergency services</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Fire brigades</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Bushfires</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ATV 10 News 28_01_13 Ted and Julia.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="62">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Tom Elliott</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>16:41 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:52</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader. Caller, Norm, says Andrews has a chance of taking the government over, after what has happened to TAFE and the industrial relations policies. He asks when they will tighten up on spending. Andrews says they would reinstate a lot of the TAFE funding.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Norm</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>ALP - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>ALP policy</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Education - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Colleges and Universities - TAFE</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Industrial Relations - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Drive 28_01_13 Andrews6.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="63">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Tom Elliott</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>16:39 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:07</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader. Caller, Mike, asks Andrews would fix the health system. Andrews says that he can&apos;t make any promises, but he will be honest at the time. Andrews says Labor put out a jobs plan last year. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Mike</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>ALP - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>ALP policy</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Health Care - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Drive 28_01_13 Andrews5.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="64">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Tom Elliott</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>16:37 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:04</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader. Caller, Gary, asks Andrews what he would do if he got back into power. He says the pipeline doesn&apos;t work anymore and that Baillieu has been left with no money at all. He adds that all he does is criticise him. Andrews says these accusations about finances are wrong. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Gary</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>ALP - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>ALP policy</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Baillieu Government</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Budget - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Drive 28_01_13 Andrews4.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="65">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Tom Elliott</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>16:36 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:20</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader. Elliot talks about the Victorian government&apos;s plan to do a bin audit, asking if it is a good use of government funds. Andrews says it is probably worthy, but the funding may be better spend in an area such as education, especially in the wake of spending cuts. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Baillieu Government</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Budget - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Waste management</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Drive 28_01_13 Andrews3.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="66">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Tom Elliott</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>16:28 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:45</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader. Caller, Trish, says she cannot believe the arrogance of the Labor Party. She asks Andrews why Julia Gillard cut the money they should receive. Elliot says the GST revenue should be distributed on a per capita basis. Andrews says it&apos;s important to put forward a case for more revenue and have a constructive dialogue about it. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Trish</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Federal State Financial Relations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Goods and Services Tax</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Drive 28_01_13 Andrews2.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="67">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Tom Elliott</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>16:23 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>4:56</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Elliot speaks with Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader. Elliot asks Andrews if the Victorian government should intervene with how cyclists and pedestrians interact. Andrews suggests that cyclists get more education on the issue. Elliot mentions a Channel 7 &apos;phone poll found that Labor led the Coalition in Victoria on the primary vote. Andrews says that the polls suggest that people are struggling to understand what drives Ted Baillieu. He thinks the cuts in hospitals, schools, TAFE and general job losses have caused voters to question their vote. Andrews says that health should be a priority, citing long waiting lists. He says that Baillieu promised to make the teachers in the state the highest paid in the country and has systematically failed to deliver on this. Elliot says that Tony Abbott is wanting the people of Australia to voice their opinions on what his policies should include. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Baillieu Government</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Baillieu, Ted [Biography]</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Political polling</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Liberal Party - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Liberal Party policy</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Government inaction</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Drive 28_01_13 Andrews1.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="68">
<inm:StationProg>ABC News Radio</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Steve Chase</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>11:23 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>3:34</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>There are calls for the establishment of a dedicated family drug treatment court, based on similar courts with proven outcomes in the US and UK. Greg Levine, Children&apos;s Court of Victoria Magistrate, has seen the damaging long-term effects of separating children from their parents, for the most part, due to long term substance abuse. He explains the family drug treatment court is an essentially non-adversarial court process headed by a judicial officer but it involves a multi-disciplinary team of professionals who work with families where there are substance abuse issues. He says the aim of the court will be to reunite children with their rehabilitated drug using parents within twelve months. Levine visited the courts as part of a Churchill fellowship in 2011. He says there are over 3,000 new protection applications each year in the Children&apos;s Court of Victoria and about 70% of those cases involve parents with significant substance abuse issues, who are therefore unable to look after their children effectively. He adds that children are removed and often never return, which is an enormous problem for our community in terms of the cost, both economic and social. He is proposing a pilot be set up within the Children&apos;s Court of Victoria by the end of the year. He says the system really is not working for these families where there are substance abuse issues. He says in his view, it should be the highest priority for governments to be able to introduce this court process. He has floated the idea with the Justice Department and Victoria&apos;s Department of Human Services. Victoria&apos;s Community Services Minister, Mary Wooldridge, welcomes the initiative. Wooldridge says the Baillieu Government is very interested in that idea and is looking at the model and seeing if that&apos;s something that would fit well into the Victorian justice system. Levine envisages the pilot program would run over three years. He says if the pilot is successful, the family drug treatment court would be recognised through legislation as an integral part of the family division of the Children&apos;s Court of Victoria.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Greg Levine, Children&apos;s Court of Victoria Magistrate</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Mary Wooldridge, Victorian Community Services Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Courts</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Court procedures</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Drug abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Children&apos;s courts</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/ABC News Radio 28_01_13 Family drugs.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="69">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Justin Smith</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>09:09 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>7:37</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Smith says the Supreme Court recently granted a reprieve to two dogs deemed American pit bull terriers. The Victorian Civil and Administrative Tribunal [VCAT] agreed with the two councils involved, Monash and Darebin, that the dogs fitted the legal definition. The councils have been ordered to pay $200,000 in legal fees in a move suspected to deter similar councils. Peter Walsh, Victorian Agriculture Minister, knew the case was pending but learned of the outcome through the media. Walsh tells Smith that changes made recently meant &apos;quite a number of dogs were taken off the street&apos; and put down. Walsh acknowledges further changes may now be needed, and says councils have a responsibility under the Domestic Animals Act for the control of pet dogs and rules around them. Walsh does not wish to comment on their Supreme Court ruling, but will review the situation. Walsh notes VCAT upheld the decision the councils made, but the Supreme Court ruled otherwise. Walsh tells Smith that if further change is needed, he is prepared to do that. Smith tells Walsh he has not offered anything new in the interview and asks what he and Victorian Premier, Ted Baillieu, want to do about it. Walsh says the key issue is that the state government is prepared to make changes that are necessary to give councils the power to enforce the rules around dangerous dogs. Walsh suggests that changes to both the Domestic Animals and Crimes Acts are on the table, and the Victorian Coroner is contributing to discussions.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Peter Walsh, Victorian Agriculture Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Law reform</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Dangerous dogs</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Local Government - Regulations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 28_01_13 Peter Walsh.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="70">
<inm:StationProg>ABC Radio AM</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Tony Eastley</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>28 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>08:22 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>3:35</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>There are calls today for the establishment of a dedicated family drug treatment court, to reunite children with their rehabilitated drug using parents within twelve months. Victorian Children&apos;s Court Magistrate, Greg Levine, visited similar courts in the US, as part of a Churchill Fellowship. Levine wants a trial set up for the Victorian Children&apos;s Court by the end of the year. He says a dedicated family drug treatment court would meet two of Victoria&apos;s recommendations from the Cummins Inquiry, including that child protection move away from an adversarial system. Victorian Community Services Minister, Mary Wooldridge, welcomes the idea.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Greg Levine, Victorian Children&apos;s Court Magistrate</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Mary Wooldridge, Victorian Community Services Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Courts</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Court procedures</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Drug abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Children&apos;s courts</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/ABC Radio AM 28_01_13 Family Court and drugs.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="71">
<inm:StationProg>ABC TV News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Tamara Oudyn</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>27 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>19:14 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:56</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>The Victorian government vows to amend dangerous dog laws, after the Supreme Court ruled two Melbourne councils wrongly classified dogs as pit-bulls. VCAT had given Darebin and Monash councils approval last year to destroy two American pit-bull terriers.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Allie Jalbert, RSPCA spokeswoman</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Micaela Drieberg, City of Monash Mayor</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Law reform</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Dangerous dogs</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Local Government - Regulations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ABC 1 News 27_01_13 Dog laws fail.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="72">
<inm:StationProg>GTV 9 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Alicia Loxley</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>27 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:15 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:30</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Melbourne roads are becoming clogged with junk, due to unsecured loads, causing a costly headache for VicRoads and a hazard for motorists.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Steven Bevans, VicRoads Traffic Commander</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Terry Mulder, Victorian Transport Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Roads - Melbourne</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Waste management</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Litter</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/GTV 9 News 27_01_12 Road junk.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="73">
<inm:StationProg>HSV 7 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>27 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:10 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:33</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>The Baillieu Government is vowing to do all it can to ensure the state gets rid of dangerous dogs, after the Supreme Court overturned a decision to put down two dogs deemed restricted breeds by Darebin and Monash Councils. Both dogs have been returned to their owners. The case has highlighted the difficulties in identifying dogs believed to be restricted breeds. Both Councils have been ordered to pay more than $200,000 in legal costs.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Law reform</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Dangerous dogs</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Local Government - Regulations</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/HSV 7 News 27_01_13 Dangerous dogs.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="74">
<inm:StationProg>GTV 9 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Alicia Loxley</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>27 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:09 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:31</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier, has launched a new campaign aimed at getting Victorians to exercise, the &apos;Active Families Challenge&apos;. Research shows over a quarter of Victorian children aged five to seventeen are considered overweight or obese. Dieticians say the family fitness approach is positive, but healthy eating also needs to a priority.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Anita Drake, mother</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Miriam Raleigh, paediatric dietician</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Public awareness campaigns</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Health</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/GTV 9 News 27_01_13 Active families.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="75">
<inm:StationProg>HSV 7 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Mitchell</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>27 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:08 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:45</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>A Seven News poll has shown Victorian Premier, Ted Baillieu, is in trouble, with Daniel Andrews the preferred premier over Baillieu. Baillieu has been promoting his &apos;Active Families Challenge&apos; at Melbourne Park, but Victorians are not warming to him. Baillieu says he does not comment on polls, but that there have been enormous challenges and he is meeting those challenges. Voters are concerned about the teachers, nurses, police and public servants disputes. He has also had to deal with controversial Frankston Liberal MP, Geoff Shaw. Daniel Andrews is also preferred premier, a rare feat for an Opposition leader during a first term.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Daniel Andrews, Victorian Opposition leader</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Ted Baillieu, Victorian Premier</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Baillieu Government</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Baillieu, Ted [Biography]</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Opposition Leaders</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Andrews, Daniel [Biography]</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Political polling</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/HSV 7 News 27_01_13 Ted polls badly.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="76">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Darren James and Bill Kusznirczuk</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>26 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>11:52 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:36</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with with Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister. Caller, Julie, says her dad chose their house in St Albans by jumping on the first tram that came. Kusznirczuk advises caller to read story in the Herald Sun by the chair of the Australia Day Committee, Stefan Romaniw.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Julie</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Immigration</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Migrants</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Housing - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 26_01_13 Kotsiras8.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="77">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Darren James and Bill Kusznirczuk</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>26 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>11:50 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>2:25</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with with Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister. Caller, Josephine, says her dad worked at Eildon weir and saved up to buy a house in Richmond. They are Italian. Kotsiras, James and Kusznirczuk are unable to remember the name of that Leo Sayer song. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Josephine</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Immigration</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Migrants</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Housing - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 26_01_13 Kotsiras7.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="78">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Darren James and Bill Kusznirczuk</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>26 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>11:44 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:45</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with with Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister. Caller, Ray, came over from England in 1971. His mother begged him not to became an Australian citizen while she lived. [cont.]
</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Ray</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Citizenship</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 26_01_13 Kotsiras5.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="79">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Darren James and Bill Kusznirczuk</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>26 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>11:44 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:02</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with with Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister. Kotsiras responds to caller, Brian, by asserting that he describes himself as an Australian, not a Greek-Australian, or some such. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Brian</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Citizenship</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 26_01_13 Kotsiras6.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="80">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Darren James and Bill Kusznirczuk</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>26 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>11:43 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:37</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with with Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister. Caller, Leigh, is a Hawthorn supporter. Kotsiras notes that former Hawthorn president Jeffrey Kennett was his old boss. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Leigh</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Sport - AFL</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 26_01_13 Kotsiras4.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="81">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Darren James and Bill Kusznirczuk</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>26 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>11:41 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:46</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with with Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister. Caller, Gary, came to Australia from England in 1956 and was conscripted into the armed services. He wants to become an Australian citizen and would have thought he could just go in and get it after all this time. Kotsiras notes that migrants who have just arrived are encouraged to engage with the community and participate, where it&apos;s the local Rotary Club, school council or SES. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Gary</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Citizenship</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 26_01_13 Kotsiras3.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="82">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Darren James and Bill Kusznirczuk</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>26 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>11:40 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>0:47</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Continuing interview with with Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister. Caller, Judy, is in Sydney Road [Brunswick] selling the &apos;Big Issue&apos; and has noticed for the first time that the trams are flying the Australian flag. Kotsiras affirms his support for the current Australian flag. [cont.]
</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Caller, Judy</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Flags</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 26_01_13 Kotsiras2.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="83">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Mornings</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Darren James and Bill Kusznirczuk</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>26 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>11:35 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>5:50</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Interview with Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister. Kotsiras says he attended the Manningham council citizenship ceremony this morning. He notes English migrants tend to wait the longest before becoming citizens. He and Kusznirczuk mention the activities at Princes Pier. Kotsiras asks Kusznirczuk what&apos;s wrong with the Melbourne Airport Corporation. He asks comperes how they think Melbourne airport compares with others around the world. It&apos;s no good, declares James. He flew Tiger during the week and it&apos;s like a sheep shed - you have to walk to the domestic terminal to get the SkyBus. [cont.]</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Nick Kotsiras, Victorian Multicultural Affairs Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Citizenship</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Aviation - Airports</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Mornings 26_01_13 Kotsiras1.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="84">
<inm:StationProg>HSV 7 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Rebecca Maddern</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>25 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:19 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:55</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Hospital emergency departments across Victoria will be &apos;beefed-up&apos; to cope with an increasing number of drug and alcohol related cases. It&apos;s part of a Victorian government strategy to fight drug and alcohol abuse. Violence erupted this afternoon outside a hotel in Abbotsford. The collective cost to the Victorian economy of such incidents is more than $6 billion. Ambulances are kept busy, with 14,000 annual call- outs for drug and alcohol cases, including prescription drugs. The Victorian government is also pressing the federal government to consider a ban on alcohol being advertised on television.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Jessie Cooke, former drug addict</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Mary Wooldridge, Victorian Community Services Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Professor Russell Gruen, Alfred Hospital spokesman</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Drug abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Alcohol abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Hospital emergency departments</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/HSV 7 News 25_01_13 Drug abuse plan.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="85">
<inm:StationProg>GTV 9 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Peter Hitchener</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>25 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>18:15 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:34</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Head trauma surgeon at the Alfred hospital welcomes a Victorian government plan to reduce deaths and injuries caused by drugs and alcohol. Specialist staff to be placed in twenty-one emergency departments to treat intoxicated patients. The state government is considering seeking federal government support.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Jessie Cooke, former drug addict</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Mary Wooldridge, Victorian Community Services Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Russell Gruen, Alfred hospital spokesman</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Drug abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Alcohol abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Hospital emergency departments</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/GTV 9 News 25_01_13 Drug abuse plan.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="86">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Lindy Burns</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>25 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:23 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>8:39</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Burns interviews The Age Editor-in-Chief, Andrew Holden, about two journalists at the paper, Richard Baker and Nick McKenzie, who have lost an appeal to stop them from being forced to appear as witnesses in a bribery case involving the Reserve Bank bank notes subsidiary, Securency. Burns presumes Baker and McKenzie are being asked to reveal the source of the numerous stories they have written about the bribery allegations. Holden says the Victorian Parliament has since changed the law to provide journalists with protection in such cases.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Andrew Holden, The Age Editor-in-Chief</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Court procedures</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Newspapers</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Journalism</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Drive 25_01_13 Andrew Holden.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="87">
<inm:StationProg>ATV 10 News</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Steven Quartermain</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>25 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:17 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>1:42</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Police have warned they will be out in force over the Australia Day long weekend. The Victorian government today released a fifteen point plan to reduce drug harm, after it was revealed 625 Victorians died from drug and alcohol abuse in 2010, costing the state around $6.5 billion.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Jessie Cooke, former drug addict</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Mary Wooldridge, Victorian Community Services Minister</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Professor Russell Gruen, Alfred Hospital spokesman</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Interviewee>Robert Hill, Victoria Police Assistant Commissioner</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Police - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Driving offences</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Drink driving</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Drug abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Alcohol abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile />
<inm:Videofile>2013/ATV 10 News 25_01_13 Police blitz.asx</inm:Videofile>
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="88">
<inm:StationProg>3AW Drive</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Tom Elliott</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>25 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>17:09 PM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>5:23</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary>Elliott welcomes Victorian Mental Health Minister, Mary Wooldridge, to discuss a fifteen point, Victorian government plan to reduce the toll of drugs and alcohol. Wooldridge says the whole-of-government plan entails alcohol policy, misuse of pharmaceutical and illicit drugs and treatment services, but it also engages with community and emergency services, such as police. Wooldridge says it deals with drugs, both as criminal and medical problems. Elliott notes a &apos;DrinkWise Australia&apos; survey finds alcohol consumers retain a cavalier attitude toward their own drinking. Wooldridge says there is a lot of merit in this survey, then she discusses a new online alcohol consumption tool - &apos;Say When&apos;.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Mary Wooldridge, Victorian Minister for Mental Health</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Alcohol abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Drug abuse</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3AW Drive 25_01_13 Wooldridge.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="89">
<inm:StationProg>3CR</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Philippe Perez, Jonathan Brown and Sally Willmot</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>25 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>07:30 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>5:41</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Interview with Greg Barber, Leader, Victorian Greens. The host says a secret strategy report states that the $5.3 billion V/Line Regional Rail Link, set to open over 2016 - 2018, will not have capacity to transport the expected number of commuters. She says the report recommends that waiting rooms will need to be opened in Kyneton and Woodend. She reports the Greens are putting pressure on the Victorian Government to expand the project. Barber says the Regional Rail Link is supposed to increase the number of trains coming from the western suburbs, and allow more services to Geelong, Ballarat and Bendigo. He recalls in 2009, former Premier John Brumby said the project was &apos;shovel-ready&apos;. Barber says the report states that many of the services will be standing-room only from day one. He explains V/Line estimated that 50 new trains would be needed, and the Government has only ordered 40. He predicts suburbs such as Melton and Tarneit are going to expand massively over the next few years. He mentions Ararat is ignored in the plan. He recently visited Portland and heard from students who need to travel to Warrnambool in the morning. He argues there needs to be a plan for the continuous expansion of V/Line. He states both Labor and Liberal governments have &apos;run-down&apos; the V/Line system over the past 20 years.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Greg Barber, Leader, Victorian Greens</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Transport - Trains</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Transport policy</inm:Subject>
<inm:Subject>Transport infrastructure</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title>Friday Breakfast</inm:Title>
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/3CR Breakfast 25_01_13 Barber.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
<inm:Record setEntry="90">
<inm:StationProg>ABC 774 Breakfast</inm:StationProg>
<inm:Compere>Red Symons</inm:Compere>
<inm:Date>25 January 2013</inm:Date>
<inm:Time>07:25 AM</inm:Time>
<inm:Duration>5:48</inm:Duration>
<inm:Summary> Interview with Alex Chernov, Governor of Victoria, to discuss tomorrow&apos;s Open House at Government House. Chernov says the Governor is appointed at pleasure which means it can be removed at the drop of a hat on the recommendation of the Premier. He admits that Government House is a lovely place to live. He says the Queen used to stay on The Britannia but when that was decommissioned she did stay at Government House. Chernov says 15,000 visited last years Open House. He says he chairs the Executive Council Meeting every Tuesday. He says he does not interfere with the workings of the Government. He says the best thing about the job is that you meet so many Victorians that work for the betterment of the community.</inm:Summary>
<inm:Interviewee>Alex Chernov, Governor of Victoria</inm:Interviewee>
<inm:Subject>Governors - Victoria</inm:Subject>
<inm:Title />
<inm:TransURL />
<inm:ItemNo />
<inm:Audiofile>2013/774 ABC Mornings 25_01_13 GG.asx</inm:Audiofile>
<inm:Videofile />
<inm:Transfile />
</inm:Record>
</inm:Recordset>
</inm:Results>
